const data = [
    {
        question: "javascript is ______ language?",
        option1: "multithreaded",
        option2: "single threaded",
        option3: "Both A and B",
        option4: "None",
        answer:"single threaded",
    },
    {
        question: "React is javascript ______ ?",
        option1: "library",
        option2: "framework",
        option3: "Both A and B",
        option4: "None",
        answer: "library"
    },
    {
        question:"If you type the following code in the console window, what result will you get? 3 > 2 > 1 === false;",
        option1: "true",
        option2: "false",
        option3: "undefined",
        option4: "error",
        answer: "true",
    },
    {
        question:"JavaScript is a ___ -side programming language.",
        option1: "client",
        option2: "server",
        option3: "both",
        option4: "none",
        answer: "both",
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following will write the message “Hello DataFlair!” in an alert box?",
        option1: "alertBox(“Hello DataFlair!”);",
        option2: "alert(Hello DataFlair!);",
        option3: "msgAlert(“Hello DataFlair!”);",
        option4: "alert(“Hello DataFlair!”);",
        answer: "alert(“Hello DataFlair!”);",
    },
    {
        question:"How do you find the minimum of x and y using JavaScript?",
        option1: "min(x,y);",
        option2: "Math.min(x,y)",
        option3: "Math.min(xy)",
        option4: "min(xy);",
        answer: "Math.min(x,y)",
    },
    {
        question:"Which JavaScript label catches all the values, except for the ones specified?",
        option1: "catch",
        option2: "label",
        option3: "try",
        option4: "default",
        answer: "default",
    },
    {
        question:"Which are the correct “if” statements to execute certain code if “x” is equal to 2?",
        option1: "if(x 2)",
        option2: "if(x = 2)",
        option3: "if(x == 2)",
        option4: "if(x != 2 )",
        answer: "if(x == 2)",
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following function of String object returns the calling string value converted to lower case?",
        option1: "toLocaleLowerCase()",
        option2: "toLowerCase()",
        option3: "toString()",
        option4: "substring()",
        answer: "toLowerCase()",
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following function of Array object calls a function for each element in the array?",
        option1: "concat()",
        option2: "every()",
        option3: "filter()",
        option4: "forEach()",
        answer: "forEach()",
    },
]

export default data;